export const data =[
{
id: 1,
question : "What is 2+2 ?",
option: ["5","4","8"],
answer : "4"
},
{
    id: 2,
    question : "What is 3+3 ?",
    option: ["5","6","8"],
    answer : "6"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question : "What is 9+10 ?",
        option: ["5","4","19"],
        answer : "19"
        },
        {
            id: 4,
            question : "What is 5 + 2 ?",
            option: ["7","4","8"],
            answer : "7"
            },
            {
                id: 5,
                question : "What is 2 + 7 ?",
                option: ["5","4","9"],
                answer : "9"
                },
                                        
                {
                    id: 6,
                    question : "What is 7 + 4 ?",
                    option: ["5","11","8"],
                    answer : "11"
                    },
                    {
                        id: 7,
                        question : "What is 6 + 3 ?",
                        option: ["5","9","8"],
                        answer : "9"
                        },
                        {
                            id: 8,
                            question : "What is 12 + 8 ?",
                            option: ["5","14","20"],
                            answer : "20"
                            },
                            {
                                id: 9,
                                question : "What is 22 + 3 ?",
                                option: ["15","14","25"],
                                answer : "25"
                                },
                                {
                                    id: 10,
                                    question : "What is 33 + 2 ?",
                                    option: ["25","35","28"],
                                    answer : "35"
                                    },
                                                                                                                                            



]